Hey, what color do you
think Hori-senpai would like?
Chocolate Recipes
I've seen her with red
and pink things before...
Maybe that would be
better than blue or white.
Hey, are you listening?
Are you listening, Miyamura?!
Please leave.
Miyamura, you're her boyfriend!
So what color does she like?
Sawada-san, please leave.
Valentine's Day is almost here,
SNAP
and I can't wrap her present unless
I know what color ribbon to use!
Why did you come to ask me?!
Maybe you just don't understand
how important it is
for a present to be as cute
and appealing as possible.
I mean, maybe I don't, but...
The wrapping, huh?
Miyamura, don't tell me...
Are you planning to just
let the shop wrap it?
Well, not that it's any of my business.
But the shop's wrapping is cute...
How do you do it, Sawada?
Hmm, what color should I pick?
Hori-san likes red and orange.
That'll do.
Chocolate
This wrapping is simple and
looks cute, don't you think?
Katagiri High School
Good morning, Sawada-san.
Good morning.
G-Good morning.
Oh, right. I need to figure out
where to buy a ribbon.
Kyon-Kyon, you're gonna give
Miyamura-kun a Valentine, right?
Nope, he said he's making one for me.
Miyamura-kun's family
owns a cake shop, right?
I bet he'll make something really nice.
What about you, Kyon-Kyon?
Me?
I don't think I can make a very good dessert.
Oh. That's kinda selfish.
Stare
I mean, mine would pale
in comparison to Miyamura's,
Famous Pâtissier
and it won't feel right to give him
one from a different shop.
Big-Chain Bakery
That's the wrong way to think about it.
The last cake she made was burned to a crisp
Smolder Smolder
He'll be so disappointed.
He doesn't want to be gifted
a crappy dessert!
I think he'd be happy
to receive anything you made.
I still think a good dessert would be better.
The one on this page, okay?
Okay.
Oh, Sawada-san?
WHIP
Hori-senpai!
You over here for class?
Zoom
No, I just needed to show Miyamura something.
But, say, it's almost time, isn't it?
I'll do my best this year!
Huh?
I got Miyamura to tell me—
WH
AP
Wriggle Struggle
Come on, Sawada-san.
You don't want to be late for class.
What're you doing?!
I can't have her finding out
I can't decide on the gift wrap!
Hori-senpai!
What was that about?
No idea.
Gosh!
He could be a little more understanding!
I'm getting mad just thinking about it!
Um, Sawada-san?
Yes?
Um, you're friends with
the third-years, right?
This again?
Yeah, I am.
What about it?
Valentine's Day is coming up.
Yeah.
So I was, um...
There's a third-year boy...
Yanagi
Well... he's pretty cool
Miyamura
Well... he's not bad
Which one?
Huh? Wh-Which one?
You mean Yanagi or Miyamura, right?
I can pass a present to either one.
Wh-Who are Yanagi and Miyamura?
An underclassman
says she likes him,
I think...
Ishikawa
Well... he stands out
Sengoku
Ishikawa?
Sengoku?
S-Sorry, I don't know them either.
Sorry, then it might be a boy I don't know.
Oh, I see.
He comes to school in a hoodie all the time.
Oh, you mean Iura...
SHOCK
Wait, Iura?!
Oh, I'm sorry. Do you also happen to...
No, it's not like that.
I-It's just... Iura?
The loudmouth in the hoodie?
Yeah.
Rude
Seriously?
Yeah.
So his name is Iura-senpai?
Gosh, I'm blushing...
I've never spoken to him, and he
probably doesn't know who I am,
GUSH GUSH GUSH
but I thought giving him
some chocolate wouldn't hurt.
He won't be here next year anyway.
O-Okay, it's all good. Just calm down.
Will he still accept it
if he has a girlfriend?
He doesn't have a girlfriend.
R-Really?
Not even secretly?
Trust me.
Do you want to date him? Why not tell him?
D-Don't get the wrong idea.
I j-just want to give him
some chocolate. Th-That's all.
I'm glad.
I couldn't ask anyone in class.
I really wanted to tell someone.
Talking about it gets me sort of flustered.
I-I'll listen, even if I can't do much.
U-Um, I'd like you to ask what
kind of chocolate he likes.
You really only want to
give him some chocolate?
Yeah.
So you respect him.
That's it. That sounds right.
Student Council
The supermarkets and convenience stores are
gonna start pushing Valentine's Day stuff.
I feel you.
But since you're probably gonna get a ton
of chocolate and I'm not, I don't feel you!
You just said you did.
Anyway, what are you two doing?
Beats me.
Practicing tying a tie, maybe?
Miyamura can already tie a tie, right?
I'm pretty sure he can.
Done!
Messy
Wait... It's not cute at all.
What's this supposed to be?
I thought I followed the directions
from Sawada's magazine...
What even is this?
Damn, the knot's too tight!
I can't get it out, Miyamura!
Hey, it's Sawada-san!
What's up?
Want me to get Miyamura?
N-No.
Sawada?
I'm here to see...
Iura.
Huh? Me?
Why?
Um, do you like... chocolate?
C-Could this be...
in preparation for Valentine's Day?
S-Sure, I like chocolate.
Any flavor in particular?
I like them all.
I don't have any allergies,
and I can do sweet or bitter.
Everyone can see how desperate you are, Shu.
Any kind of chocolate is fine.
Okay, thanks.
Glance
Any kind at all!
Sawada-san, are you
gonna give Shu chocolate?
I thought it'd just be Hori-san.
H-H-Hey! Don't discourage her, you guys!
Don't let them give you a hard time, okay?
Recoil
Why would I give chocolate to Iura?
That's crazy.
Anyway, I'm heading back to class.
Huh? Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What was that?!
Confused
She's toying with your heart, Shu.
I knew something didn't seem right.
He said he likes any kind of chocolate.
That's good. That means I can
take my time picking some out.
There are so many kinds, it's hard to choose.
I didn't expect so many.
Thanks for coming with me.
It's nothing.
I'm giving someone chocolate, too,
so I wanted to see what they have.
Who are you giving chocolate?
I-It's a secret!
If I'm not able to give it to him,
will you accept it instead?
Don't worry. You can do it!
You're doing this for real!
I'll do my best.
Valentine's Day is coming up.
I think he'd be happy
to receive anything you made.
Okay.
Library
Wh...
What's the easiest chocolate dessert to make?
Oh, are you making
a Valentine for Miyamura-kun?
Shh! Someone might hear!
It's okay. There's no one else here.
I figured it would be best
not to ask the person I'm giving it to.
I know I won't be able to make
something nice like they sell in shops.
But if there's a dessert I can't screw up...
Am I really gonna give the simplest dessert
possible to a cake shop owner's son?
Conflicted
As simple as possible, but still delicious...
Hang on.
Simple Desserts to Make at Home
A recipe book? I didn't know
the library had those.
They do.
And this one's easy to follow, too.
When I started making desserts,
I borrowed this book a lot.
Chocolate desserts are... here, on this page.
I think this one might work.
Kono-san's desserts are fantastic,
Simple Desserts to Make at Home
but I guess even she started somewhere.
BAM
BOOM
BANG
POW
Okay!
Kyoko-chan, can I eat this?
Get out!
Honey, let Kyoko be when
she's wielding a knife.
Is she preparing for battle?
Big Sis, what are you making?
It's dangerous, so wait over there.
Is it a special occasion?
Not really.
I'm just practicing for Valentine's Day.
She says she's practicing for
Valentine's Day with that scary face!
Is she gonna fight someone?
Dang it! I'll bring it to you when it's done,
so let me concentrate!
Scary!
I only look scary because
I'm taking this so seriously.
Miyamura will like it more
if it tastes good.
It's not really good.
I... I... I see...
Sota, you dummy!
I-I'll have one, too!
No, don't!
I'll try one.
I think I will as well.
No, don't!
It's not so bad.
I just can't eat a lot of it.
It's not terrible?
I can see why Sota wouldn't like it.
It's not too sweet.
It's perfect for me, though.
I'll have another.
Hey, Yuri-chan's going for the biggest one!
I-It's good?
It depends on your taste.
BA-BAM
Tell me if it's good or not!
Glooooom
A-Are you okay, Hori-san?
I must be lacking taste.
That kind of thinking won't get you anywhere.
I don't think you need to worry.
Guys don't mind things a little bitter.
Tell it to me straight!
I promise not to fly into a rage.
You're already getting hysterical!
I didn't even cut them right.
Hori-san, remember what Remi said?
He'll be happy to receive anything you made.
It not how it looks or how
it tastes that matters most.
And personally, I like this chocolate.
It reminds me of you.
Kono-san...
Hori-san, why are you behind me?
She's right. The most important thing is...
Happy Valentine's Day.
I'm blushing.
Thanks.
J-Just so you know,
I'm giving them to everyone!
I know. It's fine.
Iura-kun! Here's your obligatory chocolate.
At least say it's friend-to-friend.
Hey, it's Miyamura brand!
Remember our shop's name, please.
Hey, Miyamura, I want some, too!
Looks like Miyamura-kun brought more
chocolate than the girls.
Coming!
You're telling me.
Hori-san.
Can you come over today?
Sure.
Can I come after school?
Yeah. Oh!
But I'm heading home early,
so take your time.
Okay, then I'll stop by my place first.
Let me know if it starts to
get dark. I'll come get you.
I'll be fine.
Then I'll see you later.
It's gotta be chocolate.
He said he'd make me some.
But he almost always comes to our place...
Giant Chocolate Fondue Tower
Wow!
Did he make something huge?
What is it? I'm dying to know!
Hori-senpai!
Happy Valentine's Day!
This is for you!
I worked really hard on it!
Th-Thank you.
So this is what she said
she'd try her best on.
Wow, it's so cute!
You really think so?
I'm so glad!
I love the color of this ribbon.
I'm almost sad to open it.
Miyamura told me what colors you like.
He said you'd definitely like that one.
I hated that I needed his help, but...
What I like...
I see.
I love it. Thank you.
Maybe hoping to see someone you like
with a happy look on their face
is what today is really about.
Good, you're here! Package for you!
What is it?
Chocolate delivery.
I'm giving them to everyone,
so they're not very big,
but they came out better than last year!
Smells funny
I'll eat mine at home!
S-So will I.
Don't wait too long to eat them. Bye!
It's like a storm passed through.
Yeah.
Yoshikawa-san!
Kono-san?
Um, I didn't get a chance to give you this.
Here.
Okay, I'll give it to him.
Thanks, but...
Well, look inside later.
Bye.
Is it okay to look inside?
Ishikawa-kun
There are two boxes.
Yuki
Kono-san...
S-Sakura...
Pardon me.
Am I early?
Nope, you're right on time.
Have a seat.
Where's your mom?
She should be home soon.
What if he doesn't like them?
Miyamura's so nice. He'll probably
say he likes them even if he doesn't.
Thanks for waiting.
Miyamura—
Happy Valentine's.
Oooh
I tried making a Valentine cake.
It smells so good!
Can I eat it?
Okay, I will! Thank you!
Delicious as always!
I'm so glad you like it.
Why? Were you worried about it?
Not worried exactly...
Truth is, I couldn't decide how to wrap it.
I would've brought it to your house otherwise.
Sorry that it's so plain.
I brought the chocolate I made
without any kind of wrapping.
Tremble
Not at all... I really like it...
Really?
It's too late to worry now.
Actually, I made something, too.
Shake
What? You made something for me?
I'm sure you already know it won't be
nearly as good as yours.
Why are you being so self-critical?
Droop
Wow, chocolate ganache.
I love ganache.
I should've known...
Depressed
Happy
On special occasions, you make
something by hand and wrap it with care.
I was only thinking about him eating it.
Oh, this plate is from your house.
Kinda puts me at ease.
He's eaten a bunch of it.
Do you like it?
I do.
It's just sweet enough.
Want to try one, Hori-san?
Here. Say, "Aah."
Pretty good, right?
I guess...
It's better than my practice ones.
It's hard to relax until you see
how your partner reacts.
So he felt the same way...
How is the cake?
It's delicious, obviously.
You made it, after all.
Thank goodness.
How am I supposed to eat
with you staring at me?
Oh, sorry.
Chocolate cake that
simply melts in your mouth.
Whipped cream that isn't too sweet.
Just how I like it.
What should I make next year?
It's too soon for that.
You'll eat it, right?
Of course I will.
It's something that only I'll get to taste.
What are you gonna make for me?
I don't need to make anything anymore.
You were so cute,
looking worried all this time.
Don't mind that!
How could I not?
Miyamura put his heart into that dessert.
It tasted like happiness.
Next time
page.12 Hori's House
Oh, Sawada-san.
The third-years are going home soon.
Yeah.
I just can't do it after all.
I can't even talk to the boys in my class.
I'm just making up excuses.
All after you were such a big help...
I'm sorry.
I can give it to—
That's not the issue here.
She wanted to give it to him herself.
Now this will go to waste.
But I was so excited,
and that was really fun.
Thank you.
Okay, then give me the chocolate!
You said I could have it
if you didn't give it to him.
That way, it won't go to waste.
I'll eat all of it.
Really?
You'll really eat it?
Okay, then...
Here.
Thanks.
And this... is from me.
I bought it yesterday.
I guess it's obligatory chocolate or whatever.
Thank you, Sawada-san.
But this isn't obligatory chocolate.
Hoping you have a Happy Valentine's Day.
-Sawada
It's friendship chocolate.